<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sights and Sounds</string>
    <!--Text for location selection-->
    <string name="select_location">Select a location</string>
    <!--Name text for Calabar-->
    <string name="calabar">Calabar</string>
    <!--Header text for Historical attraction fragment-->
    <string name="historical">History</string>
    <!--Header text for attractions TabLayout-->
    <string name="attractions">Attractions</string>
    <!--Header Text for Natural attractions-->
    <string name="natural_att">Nature</string>
    <!--Header text for lodgings fragment-->
    <string name="hotspots">Hot Spots</string>
    <!--Header Text for Art fragment-->
    <string name="art">Art</string>
    <!--Header text for Tab Activity-->
    <string name="activity_tab">Tabs</string>
    <!--Name text for Proceed button-->
    <string name="proceed">Proceed</string>

    <!--Name text for Amber hotel-->
    <string name="hotel_amber">Amber Hotel</string>
    <!--Name text for Obudu Ranch-->
    <string name="lodge_obudu">Obudu Ranch Lodge</string>
    <!--Name text for Azari hotel-->
    <string name="hotel_azari">Azari Hotels</string>
    <!--Name text for Transcorp hotel-->
    <string name="hotel_transcorp">Transcorp Hotel</string>
    <!--Name Text for Hotel Five-Two-Zero-->
    <string name="hotel_five_two_zero">Hotel 520</string>

    <!--Name text for Obudu-->
    <string name="obudu">Obudu </string>
    <!--Name text for Obudu Montain Resort-->
    <string name="obudu_montain">Obudu Mountain Resort</string>
    <!--Obudu details text-->
    <string name="obudu_dets">
        Aloft in the clouds, the Obudu Mountain Resort (formerly known as the Obudu Cattle Ranch)
        is a ranch and resort on the Obudu Plateau in Cross River State, Nigeria.\n
        It was developed in 1951 by M. McCaughley,
        a Scot who first explored the mountain ranges in 1949.\n
        Today, the Obudu Montain Resort is one of the most visited location is Nigeria with its
        awe-inspiring landscapes and breath-taking scenery
    </string>
    <!--Name Text for Cross River State-->
    <string name="cross_river">Cross River State </string>
    <!--CrossRiver Details-->
    <string name="cross_dets">
        Cross River is one of Nigeria\'s 36 states.\n
        It is located southeast of the country at Biafrabukta and was founded in 1967.\n
        Previously, it was part of the Eastern Region and in the period 1967 to 1976 it was the South-Eastern State.\n
        In 1987, the area that became part of Akwa Ibom State was divorced.\n
        The state is named after River Cross . The state administration center is located in the city ​​of Calabar .</string>

    <!--Name text for Ikom-->
    <string name="ikom">Ikom</string>
    <!--Name text for Agbokim falls-->
    <string name="agbokim_falls">Agbokim Falls</string>
    <!--Agbokim falls details-->
    <string name="agbokim_dets">
       Nicknamed, \"The smoke that thunders\", this gem of nature is situated about 17 kilometers
        from Ikom and 315 kilometers from Calabar in the Etung local Council area of Cross River State is Agbokim Waterfalls,
        which is made up of seven streams.\n
        Surrounded by steep hills and valleys, which are encircled in a rainbow-like atmosphere;
        Agbokim fall remains one of the best destinations in Cross River State and Nigeria.\n
        The closeness of the Waterfalls to a neighbouring Cameron provides revelers an ample
        opportunity of having cross-border experience.\n
        The waterfall is made up of seven streams, which chutes over steep cliff, providing
        a seven faced falls. It sits on the cross river and descends in terraces,
        through the tropical rainforest; which itself, is picturesque, as it always looks lush and green.
    </string>

    <!--Name text for Akampka-->
    <string name="akamkpa">Akamkpa</string>
    <!--Name Text for Afi Mountain Wildlife Sanctuary-->
    <string name="afi_sanctuary">Afi Mountain Wildlife Sanctuary</string>
    <!--Text for Afi details-->
    <string name="afi_dets">
        Formerly part of the Afi River Forest Reserve, the Afi Mountain Wildlife Sanctuary was
        established in 2000 to provide improved protection to important populations of several
        endangered species including the critically endangered Cross River gorilla,
        the Nigeria-Cameroon chimpanzee, the drill and the grey-necked Picathartes or rockfowl.\n
        Afi is covered by roughly 100km² of lowland and sub-montane forest with rocky peaks
        rising to altitudes of 1,300m.\n
        On the western flank of the mountain is a large
        grassland roost of migratory European barn swallows, estimated to contain up to 20 million
        birds at times and reputed to be the largest wintering roost site of swallows in Africa.\n
        The Afi Mountain has been identified as an IBA
        (Important Bird Area) for Nigeria. It is also a significant and widely recognized spot
        in Africa to watch the migration of large swallows. This indeed is a location for those
        seeking to experience a whole new world.
    </string>

    <!--Name text for Tinapa resort-->
    <string name="tinapa">Tinapa Resort</string>
    <!--Text for Tinapa details-->
    <string name="tinapa_dets">
        Situated on the outskirts of Calabar, Tinapa is an integrated Business and Leisure
        promising the best of both worlds.\n
        The resort boasts of World class conference centres as well strings of shops and malls
        for those with an eye for business.\n
        Also, it possesses a 2km beach front, a 5-star hotel, 4 Standard sized studios, an arcade park
        as well as a water park; which has a 200ft slide, for those just looking to unwind.\n
        The resort is also equipped with a light rail network to facilitate movement around its environs.\n
        Indeed, Tinapa really takes on the Herculean task of balancing work and play in its stride.
    </string>

    <!--Name text for Marina Resort-->
    <string name="marina_resort">Marina Resort</string>
    <!--Text for Marina resort Details-->
    <string name="marina_dets">
        This is one of Calabar’s major tourist destinations./n
        It is a huge and expansive resort with amazing multi-purpose facilities as well as
        unforgettable moments at place such as the Slave History Museum, a cinema house, table
        tennis court, hotel, night club, a carousel for the children, walkway and open restaurants
        where patrons can sit, relax and eat – with breathtaking views of the Calabar river.\n
        The Tortuga island is a stunning sit-in or sit-out location within the resort
        where you can grab a seat, recline and place an order while you take in the river view as
        well as the alluring smell of the long rows of trimmed flower hedges.\n
        Taking a boat cruise on the Calabar river is a fun activity to look forward.
        The beautiful cruise boat takes you round the Marina waters.
        At the other end of the river, you’ll see a small house which is built on the
        site where Mary Slessor’s former house was situated.
    </string>

    <!--String values for History Fragment-->
    <!--Name Text for Duke Town primary School-->
    <string name="duke_town">Duke Town Primary School</string>
    <!--Name text for Hope Waddell Secondary School-->
    <string name="hope_waddell">Hope Waddell Training Institution</string>
    <!--Text for Hope Waddell details-->
    <string name="hope_waddell_dets">
        Established in 1895, this is one of the oldest institutions in the Nigeria.\n
        Originally set up as a base for arriving Scottish missionaries, it quickly transformed
        into an educational and skills acquisition center.
    </string>

    <!--Name text for Mary Slessor's Residence-->
    <string name="mary_slessor">Mary Slessor\'s Residence</string>

    <!--Name text for old residency-->
    <string name="old_residency">Old Residency</string>
    <!--Text for old residency details-->
    <string name="old_recidency_dets">This was originally the residence of the highest ranked
    British personnel in Calabar. It had been transformed to the residence of the military governors
    during the military regime in Nigeria.
        \nHowever, today, it serves a different purpose of a multifaceted museum.
    </string>
    <!--Name text Slave history museum-->
    <string name="slave_history">Slave History Museum</string>
    <string name="slave_history_dets">Located in the Marina Resort along the Calabar harbour,
    the Slave History Museum shows explicitly, the travails of Nigeria slaves who were sold
    through the Calabar sea port.</string>

    <!--String values for Art Fragment-->
    <!--Name text for the Calabar Carnival-->
    <string name="calabar_carnival">Calabar Carnival</string>
    <string name="carnival_dets">
        The Calabar Carnival tagged "Africa's Biggest Street Party", is one of the highlights of the
        Cross River State Christmas festival which begins every 1 December and lasts until 31 December.\n
        The festival was created as part of the vision of making the Cross River State, Nigeria,
        the number one tourist destination for Nigerians and tourists all over the world.\n
        This event which usually holds between December 26th and 28th has boosted the cultural mosaic
        of Nigeria people while entertaining millions of spectators
        within and outside the State, and boosting industry for all stakeholders.
    </string>

    <!--Name text for Ekpe Festival-->
    <string name="ekpe_festival">Ekpe Festival</string>
    <!--Text for Ekpe festival-->
    <string name="ekpe_dets">
       Ekpe, also known as Ekpo (Ibibio: Leopard), is a secret society flourishing chiefly among
        the Efiks of the Cross River State, the Oron, of Akwa Ibom State, Nigeria, Arochukwu
         and some parts of Abia State, as well as in the diaspora, such as in Cuba and Brazil.\n
        The society is still active at the beginning of the 21st century, however, now it plays only a ceremonial role.
        There are two distinct but related societies, the primary one in the Cross River, Arochukwu,
        Akwa Ibom areas, and the secondary one among the Southern and Eastern Igbo groups.\n
        It is general belief amongst the Efik native tribe, although hardly ever substantiated,
        that the members of the Ekpe society invented the Nsibidi.
        The Ekpe festival is an annual event that usually holds on the last Saturday of the
        year in Calabar. It attracts displays from the different Ekpe societies from around the world.
    </string>

    <!--Name Text for Leboku festival-->
    <string name="leboku_fest">Leboku Festival</string>
    <!--Name text for Ugep-->
    <string name="ugep">Ugep</string>
    <string name="leboku_dets">
        Leboku is the annual New Yam Festival of the Yakurr people.\n
        The Leboku New Yam festival is peculiar to the core Yakạạ speaking communities of Idomi,
        Ugep, Ekori, Mkpani and Nko and the international version is celebrated in Ugep once in a year.\n
        This is celebrated to honor the earth goddess and the ancestral spirits of the land in Ugep,
        one of the five settlements of Yakurr.\n
        The three-week festival is the culmination of many events: the beginning of the yam harvest,
        a time to appease the gods and ancestors, a public parade of engaged maidens, a commemoration
        of events that led to the migration from the Yakurr ancestral home to the present site,
        and a period of holiday in the Yakurr traditional calendar (mid-August through mid-September).\n
        The Yakurr calendar runs from August to July. During the Leboku, people keep away from intense
        farming activities and exchange visits with their families. The Leboku is also meant to usher in peace,
        good health and prosperity.
    </string>

    <!--Name text for Ikom Monoliths-->
    <string name="ikom_monoliths">Ikom Monoliths</string>
    <!--Text for monolith-->
    <string name="monolith_dets">

    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_attractions">AttractionsActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password</string>
    <string name="resend_verification_email">Resend Verification Email</string>
    <string name="email_registration">Email Registration</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


</resources>
